import 'package:quizapp2/tools/images.dart';

import 'lessons.dart';

List<LessonModel> lessons = [
  LessonModel(icon: Images.img3, name: "C++", test: cppQuestions),
  LessonModel(icon: Images.img4, name: "Java", test: javaQuestions),
  LessonModel(icon: Images.img5, name: "Python", test: pythonQuestions),
];

List<TestModel> cppQuestions = [
  TestModel(
    question: 'What does the ++ mean in C++?',
    answerA: 'Increase',
    answerB: 'Compile',
    answerC: 'Coded',
    answerD: 'Controller',
    correctAnswer: 'Increase',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'Who developed C++?',
    answerA: 'Dennis Richie',
    answerB: 'James Gosling',
    answerC: 'Steve Jobs',
    answerD: 'Bjarne Stroustrup',
    correctAnswer: 'Bjarne Stroustrup',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'What does STL stand for in C++?',
    answerA: 'Standard Template Library',
    answerB: 'System Transaction List',
    answerC: 'System Template Library',
    answerD: 'Stack Transactional List',
    correctAnswer: 'Standard Template Library',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'What is the full form of OOP?',
    answerA: 'Object Oriented Protocol',
    answerB: 'Object Oriented Procedure',
    answerC: 'Object Oriented Programming',
    answerD: 'Object Oriented Product',
    correctAnswer: 'Object Oriented Programming',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'How to output "Hello World" in C++?',
    answerA: 'printf("Hello World");',
    answerB: 'print("Hello World");',
    answerC: 'std::cout << "Hello World";',
    answerD: 'println("Hello World");',
    correctAnswer: 'std::cout << "Hello World";',
  ),
];

List<TestModel> javaQuestions = [
  TestModel(
    question: 'What do we use to define a block of code in Java?',
    answerA: 'Curly Braces {}',
    answerB: 'Square Brackets []',
    answerC: 'Angle Brackets <>',
    answerD: 'Round Brackets ()',
    correctAnswer: 'Curly Braces {}',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'Who developed Java?',
    answerA: 'Oracle Corporation',
    answerB: 'Microsoft Corporation',
    answerC: 'Sun Microsystems',
    answerD: 'Apple Inc.',
    correctAnswer: 'Sun Microsystems',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'What is the size of a int data type in Java?',
    answerA: '8 bit',
    answerB: '16 bit',
    answerC: '32 bit',
    answerD: '64 bit',
    correctAnswer: '32 bit',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'Java programs are',
    answerA: 'Interpreted only',
    answerB: 'Compiled only',
    answerC: 'Either compiled or interpreted',
    answerD: 'Neither compiled nor interpreted',
    correctAnswer: 'Either compiled or interpreted',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'Which method must be implemented by all threads?',
    answerA: 'wait()',
    answerB: 'start()',
    answerC: 'stop()',
    answerD: 'run()',
    correctAnswer: 'run()',
  ),
];

List<TestModel> pythonQuestions = [
  TestModel(
    question: 'What is the correct file extension for Python files?',
    answerA: '.py',
    answerB: '.pyth',
    answerC: '.pt',
    answerD: '.p',
    correctAnswer: '.py',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'Who developed Python?',
    answerA: 'Guido van Rossum',
    answerB: 'Dennis Ritchie',
    answerC: 'James Gosling',
    answerD: 'Linus Torvalds',
    correctAnswer: 'Guido van Rossum',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'Python is an example of which type of programming languages?',
    answerA: 'Object oriented programming language',
    answerB: 'Procedural oriented programming language',
    answerC: 'Structured programming language',
    answerD: 'All of these',
    correctAnswer: 'All of these',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'What does the len() function do in Python?',
    answerA: 'It counts the length of a List',
    answerB: 'It counts the characters in a String',
    answerC: 'Both A and B',
    answerD: 'None of the above',
    correctAnswer: 'Both A and B',
  ),
  TestModel(
    question: 'What is used to define a block of code in Python language?',
    answerA: 'Curly braces',
    answerB: 'Parenthesis',
    answerC: 'Indentation',
    answerD: 'Quotation',
    correctAnswer: 'Indentation',
  ),
];
